玉米片杀人狂 （音同连续杀人狂）
Cereal killer.
玉米片杀人狂？
Cereal killer?
我九点前说的蠢话 比别人整天说的还多
Hey,come on,I say more dumb things before 9 a.m...than most people say all day.
怎么了？
What?
我不知道要吃什么 吃什么都会恶心
I can't find anything that I wanna eat. Everything makes me nauseous.
怀孕真够难搞的…啊，糕
I'm telling you,being pregnant is no piece of cake. Oh,cake!
不行
No.
真可怜
Honey,I'm sorry.
什么香味？是浴室传出来的
What is that smell? It's coming from the bathroom.
怀孕倒是让你多了些怪癖
Pregnancy does give you some weird cravings.
是我，菲比 这里有我想吃的东西
It's me. It's Phoebe. Listen,there's something in here I want to eat.
什么味道这么香？
What smells so good?
是新洗发精吗？番石榴香味
-ls it the shampoo? It's guava.
不是
-No.
等一下
Wait.
是我的红肠三明治吗？
Is it my bologna sandwich?
对，没错
Yes. Yes. Yes.
宝宝居然想吃红肠 宝宝想吃肉，我不能吃肉
I can't believe it. The baby wants bologna. The baby wants meat. I can't eat meat.
等一下
Wait!
也许是腌黄瓜
Maybe it's the pickle!
本集播出：“假派对”
The One With the Fake Party
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
（中央咖啡馆）
你在写什么？
What are you writing?
约书亚明天要来 既然我没胆约他
Joshua's coming in tomorrow,and since I don't have the guts to ask him out...
我决定卖他一件外套 再把纸条塞进口袋
...I'm gonna sell him a coat and put this note in the pocket.
“约书亚：有空打电话给我” “你这样的人…”
"Joshua,give me a call sometime. Guys like you...
“…永不退流行”
...never go out of style."
你刚才扔的是什么？
What did you throw away?
你们做了什么？
-Hi,guys. -What have you guys been up to?
我们去库珀・休伊特博物馆看维多利亚时期门把展
We went to see a collection of Victorian doorknobs at the Cooper-Hewitt museum.
没找我去？
Without me?
是舅舅拖我们去的 结果很有意思
My uncle dragged us there,but it turned out to be really interesting.
那些门把很华丽，你们看
They were so ornate and beautiful. Look at that.
我不知道英国的国情 但这里不能顺手牵羊
I don't know how museums work in England,but here,you're not supposed to take stuff.
这是礼品部的
I got it from the gift shop.
那里没什么防盗措施
They have really lax security there.
这是笑话
It's a joke.
（英国腔）谁还要喝茶？
Anyone for more tea?
（英国腔）那我自己叫了
No,just me then.
鹦鹉先生
Hey,Ringo.
每次艾蜜莉在，你就怪腔怪调 别闹了
Every time Emily's around,you talk like her. Would you please cut it out?
我看你喜欢喔
I think you like it.
你无法抗拒这样的我
I think you can't resist me when I do it.
你想一口…了我
You want to eat me up like a cream "pumpy."
什么？ 我不是每个英国字都会
-What? -All right,look,I don't know all the words.
我该走了，再见
Right. I've got to be off. I'll see you. Bye-bye,then.
再见
Bye-bye,then.
你们相处得很愉快
You guys seem to be having a good time.
对，她人很棒，而且很有趣
She is amazing,and she's so much fun.
跟她在一起时，我也很有趣
And you know what? When I'm with her,I'm fun!
我会跑去佛罗蒙特 你们也看到那个门把了
I do things like run off to Vermont...and you guys saw the doorknob.
我甚至报名学开直升机
I even signed up for helicopter classes.
她过两天就走了，我不必真学
She's leaving in two days. I don't have to do it.
两天？你一定很失望
Two days? You must be bummed.
她非回去不可
She's got to go back to London,
不过我早就有心理准备 我们都知道我们只有这2星期
but I've been prepared for this from the start. We both knew we had two weeks together,and then that's it.
我的每段恋情都是
Hey,that's what all my relationships are like.
罗斯他们是“双方”都知道 只有2星期
Yes,but in Ross' case,they both know in two weeks that's it.
菲比
-Pheebs! -Hello. Hello.
宝宝好啊 好啦
No,I know. Yeah.
宝宝想肉想疯了
So the baby is totally craving meat.
下午我想用素肉堡骗他 让他以为他吃到肉
I tried tricking it,and I made it a soy burger,so that maybe it'd think it was getting meat.
结果就反胃了
And I got nauseous.
也许是因为素肉堡很难吃
Maybe that's because soy burgers suck.
不过应该很营养
But I'm no obstetrician....
怀孕真难吃东西
Being pregnant is hard on your tummy.
但你有一种孕妇的光彩
At least you got that cool,pregnant-lady glow.
你要是吐一早上也会有光彩
That's sweat. You throw up all morning,you'll have that glow too.
这是你要的风衣 太好了
Okay.Here's that trench coat that you wanted. -Great.
很舒服
It's comfortable.
这可以用来装变态
You could really flash somebody in this.
不行，出了店门 才能把手放进口袋里
No. They don't want you to put your hands in the pockets until you are out of the store.
为什么？
Why not?
因为…有很多人…
Well,because...we get a lot of
真是害群之马 是啊
They ruin it for everybody.I know.
我昨晚穿那件 喀什米尔毛衣去约会
I wore that sweater on a date last night.
我离婚后第一次约会
It was the first date since the divorce.
恭喜，你爱她吗？
Congratulations. So do you love her?
她还不错，不过我也发现 我还没有心情约会
She's nice,but it made me realize...I'm just not ready to be dating.
真有意思
That's interesting.
那是什么？ 只是防盗磁条
-What was that? -Just an anti-theft device.
那这是什么？
Then what's this?
那个也要，因为这个一撕就碎
You need that too,because a thief could just tear this up.
晚上有派对 其实是5分钟后，有事快取消
We have to have a party in five minutes,so everybody cancel your plans.
你在说什么？ 怎么回事？
What's going on?
我们要帮艾蜜莉办惊喜欢送会
We have to have a bon-voyage party for Emily.
其实是为了约书亚
But it's actually for Joshua.
讨厌 都没人帮我办过假的艾蜜莉欢送会
That sucks. Nobody's ever thrown me a bon-voyage-Emily party.
他说他还没有心情约会
He said he's not ready to date.
我得找他参加派对 才能在工作之外见到他
So I had to invite him to a party if I wanted to see him outside of work.
现在我制造了一个 色诱他的完美机会
And now I have created the perfect opportunity to seduce him.
我很想当面警告约书亚
As much as I'd like to meet Josh and warn him...
但艾蜜莉和我不能参加 她会来说声再见
...Emily and I won't be here. She's gonna come by to say goodbye...
然后我安排了整晚的节目 对不起，没戏唱了
...and then I've got a special evening planned. Sorry. No party.
惊喜！
-Hello? -Surprise!
Surprise!
没有人替我办过惊喜派对
No one's thrown me a surprise party before.
这都是罗斯的主意
Well,it was all Ross' idea.
你真好
You're so sweet.
我好惊喜喔
And I'm so surprised.
你真的没料到？
You didn't know?
约书亚在那边，你怎么在这边
Why are you over here if Joshua's over there?
我想假装很难上手
I'm trying to play hard-to-get.
快，说句好笑的话
Quick! He's looking. Say something funny.
举个例子？
Like what?
什么事这么好笑？
What's so funny?
我说“举个例子”
I said,"Like what?"
真深奥
Now that's a thinker.
假装很难上手没用
This playing-hard-to-get thing is not working.
把樱桃给我，好…
Hand me those cherries.
要吃樱桃吗？ 不要，谢谢
-Care for a cherry? -No,thanks.
我可以用舌头把樱桃梗打结
I can tie one of these into a knot using just my tongue.
你还好吗？没事吧？
You okay?You all right?
我们得赶快走了
We should probably get going soon.
但是派对才刚开始
But the party's just getting started.
我们得在15分钟内 赶去四季餐厅喝酒
We have to be at The Four Seasons for drinks in 15 minutes.
然后去广场饭店吃晚饭
Then The Plaza for dinner.
那你为什么还办派对？
So why did you plan a party at the same time?
其实美国的惊喜派对都很短
Actually,American surprise parties are very short.
通常都“惊喜！” 然后就“我好惊喜喔！再见”
It's usually,"Surprise!" Then,"My God,I'm so surprised. Bye!"
但是我觉得好好玩
Ross,I'm having such a great time.
你妹说你以前会扮成老太太 举办假的茶会
Your sister told me that you used to dress up like old ladies...and host make-believe tea parties.
莫妮卡说的是吧？
Monica said that,did she?
她有没有说她小的时候
Did she tell you that when she was little...
游乐器材商增加秋千的载重量 她也是原因之一？
...she was partially responsible for new legislation...regulating the strength of swing sets?
你接下来要放什么？
Then what are you going to put on top of that?
一点蒜味肉肠 赞
-A little salami. -Oh,yeah.
蒜味肉肠上面呢？
What goes on top of the salami?
熏牛肉 太赞了
Pastrami.
你真是天才
You're a genius.
帮我拉一下拉链
Give me a hand with the zipper.
往上
Up!
你换衣服？ 对，我需要我的幸运裙
-You changed? -I decided I needed my lucky dress.
幸运是指露更多乳沟？ 我觉得是
-Lucky means more cleavage? -lt does for me.
你们看他多帅 真想一把捉过来亲下去
Look at him! He's so cute.I just want to grab him and kiss him.
但是他不知道我喜欢他
How could I kiss him without him knowing I like him?
有个办法-脱胸罩
I know how you can get him. Take off your bra.
什么？
What?
在电影《浑身是劲》里… 是《闪舞》
-This scene in Footloose -Flashdance.
对…那个水电女工 是焊接工
-Yeah. With that plumber girl? -A welder.
你是有演吗？
Were you,like,in the movie?
总之她在衣服底下脱掉胸罩 从袖子抽出来
She takes off her bra under the shirt and pulls it out the sleeve.
非常性感，而且有格调
Very sexy. And classy.
-不然你也可以用w寄生（圣诞节时女子站在其下任何人都可以吻她） -又不是圣诞节
-Or you could use mistletoe. -It's not Christmas.
转瓶子 他不是11岁
-Spin-the-bottle. -He's not 11.
谢谢你们，你们真用心
Thank you so much for this. It was so thoughtful of you.
你们要走了？
You're leaving?
对，我们还有事 我也要走了
-We have something we have to get to. -I'm gonna take off too.
先别走，留下来 我们准备了重头戏
You can't leave yet. You have to stay.We've got the whole big thing planned.
什么重头戏？
What big thing?
转瓶子的规则是，我转瓶子
Spin-the-bottle works like this: I spin the bottle.
指向甘瑟，我就要亲甘瑟
Lands on Gunther,so I would have to kiss Gunther.
就这样
All right.
谁要先？ 我先
Who wants to go first?I'll go.
欢迎来到美国
Welcome to America.
天哪
Oh,my God!
连续两次！来个舌吻吧
Two in a row! You gotta use your tongues now.
再来
All right.
太巧了
What are the odds?
够了
That's enough!
让别人玩吧
Let's let someone else play.
你不想玩干嘛来？
If you didn't want to play,then why'd you come to the party?
我来好了
All right,I'll go.
豪放女！豪放女
Somebody loose. Somebody loose.
我的人生写照
Story of my life.
我爸的人生写照
Story of my father's life.
该我
Okay,my turn.
是你！天哪
Look at that!Oh,my God.
天哪，宝宝踢了
The baby just kicked!
他会再踢的
It's okay. It's okay. If it kicked once,it'll kick again!
大家要记住刚才的位置
Everybody just remember where they were sitting.
有虫
It was a bug.
不管我多想吃 我绝不吃肉，那是冷血谋杀
It doesn't matter how much I'm craving it.You know why I'm never gonna eat meat? Because it's cold-blooded murder.Okay.
我的三明治上有菲比
There's a Phoebe on my sandwich!
菲比，你干什么？ 我没办法
What are you doing?I can't help it!
我要吃肉，宝宝要吃肉
I need the meat! The baby needs the meat.
跟别人交往要专一 除非第三者真的很辣
You know when you're dating someone...and you don't want to cheat unless it's with someone really hot?
那当然 这就对了
Totally.This is the same kind of deal.
吃肉也一样，要错…
If you're gonna do something wrong...
就要错得漂亮
...do it right.
我马上回来 好
-I'll be back in a minute. -Okay.
她真是…
She did…
你想怎样？
What are you doing to me?
我想把她带走
I'm trying to get Emily out of here,
你却一直跟她讲话 装风趣又逗她笑
and you keep talking to her......being all interesting and making her laugh.
从现在起，请你别那么风趣
I don't want you to be funny anymore.
瑞秋要我风趣 你却不要我风趣
Rachel wants me to be funny,you don't want me to be funny.
从现在起，我要有时候风趣 有时候不风趣
From now on,I'm gonna be funny sometimes,and not funny others.
感觉好多了吗？ 对，但是代价呢？
You feel better now?Yeah,but at what cost?
三餐吃肉吃半年？我会吃掉…
Six more months,three meals a day.I am going to eat,
几百万头牛
like,you know,millions of cows.
牛爸爸，牛妈妈，牛宝宝
Mommy cows,daddy cows,baby cows
我绝不吃牛宝宝，死也不吃
No. No,I will never eat baby cows. No veal!
尽量不吃
Oh,but veal.
要是我帮你平衡过来呢？ 什么？
What if I even things out for you,meat-wise?
我很会吃肉对吧？ 对
-What? -I eat a lot of meat,right?
要是在宝宝出生前，我戒吃肉
But suppose,until the baby's born,I laid off it.
就不会多死动物 你是在吃我的份
No extra animals would die. You'd be eating my animals.
你居然愿意为我这么做
I can't believe you'd do that for me.
当然愿意，我也可以吃素
Absolutely. I could be a vegetarian.
啤酒里没有肉吧？
There's no meat in beer,right?
不吃开胃菜，马上买单 还赶得上吃主菜
We can still make dinner if we skip the appetizers and ask for our check right away.
现在不能走，瑞秋要表演
We can't go now. Rachel is going to put on a skit.
我的天哪，你疯了吗？
Oh,my God! Have you lost your mind?
不，我终于想通了
I am finally thinking clearly.
我的幸运裙效果不佳
My lucky dress wasn't working out too well for me.
但这一套整整4年都百发百中
But for four years,this baby never missed.
瑞秋，我不能让你…
Wait,I can't let
我也想看热闹
Actually,I want to see what happens.
好棒的行头
Nice costume.
是啊，我想给艾蜜莉 来个美式的再见欢呼
Well,I wanted to give Emily a big American goodbye cheer.
预备…起
Ready. Okay.
给我一个E E
Give me an "E"!
给我一个M M
Give me an "M"!
给我一个I I
Give me an "I"!
给我一个L L
Give me an "L"!
给我一个Y Y
Give me a "Y"!
加起来是什么？
What do you get?
艾蜜莉！艾蜜莉…
Emily! Emily!
以上就是我的欢呼
That's me as a cheerleader!
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
有一颗牙齿松了 小意思，我有牙医
I loosened a tooth. It's no big deal. I have a dentist.
我去冰敷，失陪
I'll put some ice on it. Excuse me.
怎么办怎么办？ 你应该是毁了
-What do I do now? -I think you're done.
该脱胸罩了
Time to take off the bra.
刚才的表演很精彩 但是我得走了
That was really great.But I gotta take off.
脱~胸~罩
Take the bra off.
我陪你去拿外套
Let's go get your coat.
瑞秋是我的女朋友
Rachel's my girlfriend.
今晚蛮开心的
So this was really fun.
是啊，很开心
Yeah,it was real fun.
这件胸罩…
You know,this bra...
实在很不舒服
...is really bothering me.
这里以前是我的房间
This used to be my bedroom.
有很多回忆，很多很多回忆
A lot of memories in here. Lot of memories.
要是墙壁会说话，它们会说 “想听听往事吗？”
If these walls could talk,they'd say:"Want to hear some memories?"
你需要帮忙吗？ 不用，没问题
Need a hand?I got this all under control.
可是看起来不像
You really don't seem like you do.
算了啦！真是…
God! Forget it!
事情不该是这样的 不然应该怎样？
This is not how this was supposed to happen.What was supposed to happen?
你能不能不要看我？
Can you not look at me when I say this?
我以为要是能把你找来
I thought that if I could get you here...
我就可以@#%$你
...I could seduce you.
什么？
-Excuse me?
引诱你
-Seduce you.
我上班不穿西装 却跟你买了六套
I don't wear suits to work.And I bought six of them from you.
抱歉，我以为你有需要
I'm sorry. I thought you needed them.
我一直去找你，因为我想见你
My point is,I kept coming back because I wanted to see you.
为什么？ 因为我喜欢你
-Why? -Because I like you.
你喜欢我？
You like me?
是啊，你漂亮、聪明又成熟
I mean,you're beautiful and smart and sophisticated.
这些印象不是来自今晚
A lot of this isn't based on tonight.
但是你喜欢我？
But you like me?
这段日子以来 我们竟然一直互相喜欢
I can't believe this. All this time,I liked you and you liked me!
但是… 不要说“但是”
-But -No "but."
“但是”都没好事 停在“我们互相喜欢”就好
"But" is never good. Let's leave it at "l like you and you like me."
好，然而… 那是好听的“但是”
-Okay. However -No,that's a fancy "but."
我刚结束我的婚姻
My marriage,like,just ended.
我还没心情跟别人交往
And I'm really not ready to get into anything yet.
但是…？
But....
对不起，我需要一点时间
I'm sorry. I just need a little time.
你在这里，我在找你
There you are. I was looking for you.
约书亚走了 你和艾蜜莉可以走了
Joshua's gone,so you and Emily are free to go.
无所谓 她还在里面享受这场假派对
It's okay.She's still in there enjoying her fake party.
现在要做什么也来不及了
It's too late to do the stuff I had planned.
抱歉，我毁了你美好的夜晚
I'm sorry. I ruined your evening.
是啊
Yeah.
我出了个大丑 你有没有高兴一点？
If it makes you feel any better,I made a fool of myself.
有一点
Helps a little.
有地方让悲惨的失败者坐吗？ 坐吧
Is there room on that step for a pathetic loser?Have a seat.
对不起
-I'm so sorry. -It's okay.
没关系 反正只是一段2星期的恋情
It was just a two-week thing anyway.
我只是不想这样结束 也许你不想结束呢？
I just didn't want it to end this way.Or maybe you didn't want it to end.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你似乎真的很喜欢她
You seem to really like her.
没错
I really do.
但我能怎么办？ 我们说好只在一起2星期
But what am I going to do? We agreed it'd be a two-week thing.
不要有承诺
No commitment.
罗斯
Ross
那个女孩整晚都跟你的朋友 吵着要听你的事
That girl just spent the entire evening talking to your friends...asking to hear stories about you.
还拿莫妮卡的相簿来看
...Iooking through Monica's photo albums.
只想在一起2周才不会这么做
You don't do that if you're just in it for two weeks.
是吗？
You think?
她还有14个小时才要去机场
You've got 14 hours until she has to be at the airport.
你却坐在走廊上
And you're sitting here in a hallway...
陪一个28岁 嘴肿起来的啦啦队长
...with a 28-year-old cheerleader with a fat lip.
你说得对
You're right.
谢了
Thanks.
哪一本相簿？ 你跟一堆白化病小孩的合照
What photo album was it?I don't know. It was you and a bunch of albino kids.
他们不是白化病 那是电脑夏令营
Oh,my God! Those weren't albino kids.That was computer camp!
你是悲惨的失败者吧？ 就是我
-You're a pathetic loser,right? -Oh,yeah.
坐
Sit!
天哪，约书亚
Oh,my God. Joshua.
我刚才说我没心情…
Look...all those things I said about not being ready
不是真的？ 不，都是真的
-They're not true? -They're all true.
但是…
But....
我喜欢这个“但是”
I love that "but."
要不要进去喝杯咖啡？ 好
Do you want to go inside and get some coffee?Okay.
百发百中
Every time.
你放什么？ 熏牛肉
-What do you got there? -Pastrami.
你知道什么跟它最配？ 腌牛肉
-You know what goes good with that? -Corned beef.
我想说红肠，但腌牛肉更棒
I was going to say bologna. But that's better.
要不要放点熏火鸡肉？ 好
-How about that smoked turkey? -Okay.
妈呀
Oh,mama!
宝宝什么时候生？ 半年后
-When is the baby due? -Six months.
自然死亡的牛可以吃吧？
If a cow died of natural causes,I could have one of those,right?
我会先下手
Not if I get there first.